Guide to the Peter H. Sera papers, 1964-1986 MS2183
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Technology: Devices and Systems, 1964-1986
  - ICA (International Communications Association) Guide to University Telecommunications Programs, 1985 July 23; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ICRS-Interconnect Circuit Records System, 1980, 1982; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Intercom Systems, 1971 May 12; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Interconnection Binder-Articles, Notes, and Correspondence, 1968-1973; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Interconnection, 1972-1976; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Interconnect Engineering Letter, 1980 July 31; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - International Record Carriers, 1975 June 12; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - IOS-Internal Order for Service, 1982 January 11; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - IRM Planning and Implementation Guide for The Travelers, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - KDS-Known Down RFT Shelters, 1980; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - LDD-Local Data Distribution, 1981; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - LDD-Local Data Distribution, 1980 June 4; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Level Zero Service Summary for SBS Binder, 1978 August 10; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lotus 1-2-3 Introduction for GTE Telenet Communications Corporation Binder, 1985; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - M and C-Monitor and Command Loop, 1980 July 8; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - MAP-Maintenance and Administration Position, 1981; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Marketing Handbook-Subscriber Products for Western Electrics, 1969; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Message Services SBS Binder-Presentations, Reports, Articles, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 9(1/2))
  - Message Services SBS Binder- Presentations, Reports, Articles, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 10 (1/2))
  - Message Services Field Marketing Guidelines SBS Binder, 1982 September; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 1(1/2))
  - Message Services Field Marketing Guidelines SBS Binder, 1982 September; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 2 (2/2))
  - Miscellaneous Telecommunications Service and Equipment, 1969-1979; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - MMS-Materials Management System, 1980; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Modems and Multiplexing, 1975-1979; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - MS-Message Service, 1982-1985; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - MS(Message Service) Wire Center, 1982; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - MS(Message Service) ENFIA, Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - MS(Message Service) Specialized Carrier Switch (SCS), Front End Switch (FES), Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - MS(Message Service) 5 Year Transmission Facilities Forecast, 1982 June 15; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - MS(Message Service) Test Market, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - MS(Message Service) SCS(Specialized Carrier Switch) Implentation Binder #1, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 1(1/2))
  - MS(Message Service) SCS (Specialized Carrier Switch) Implementation Binder #1, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 2(2/2))
  - MS(Message Service) SCS(Specialized Carrier Switch) DMS-250, 1981; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 3(1/2))
  - MS(Message Service) SCS (Specialized Carrier Switch) DMS-250, 1981; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 4(2/2))
  - MS(Message Service) II-Authorization Code System, (SRD) (System Specifications), 1982; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - MS(Message Service) II Residential Service Business Plan, 1982 August-September; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - MS(Message Service) II Service Test and Field Sites, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - MS(Message Service) II Technical Operations, Schedules, and Workbooks, Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - MS(Message Service) II Trouble Report System (TRS), 1982-1985; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - MSDD-Message Service Description Document, 1981 November 23; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - MSMS-Message Service Management System, 1981 July 16; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - MTTP-Multi Transponder Test Plan, 1982 March 24; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - MTW-Multi Transponder Workaround, 1980 April 3; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - NAC-Network Access Center Configuration Procedure, 1980; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - NAC(Network Access System) Configuration Procedure NCP Binder, 1980; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NCC-Network Control Center, 1981; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - NCC(Network Control Center) Operations Guide Operational Practices, 1981 January 26; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Nearest/Next Nearest NAC Reference Stations, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Network Design and Planning, 1979; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Network Design (Document #5), 1981 May 22; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Network Installation Process Description, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Bell System Customer Training Center Manual, 1972-1974; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 1(1/3))
  - New Jersey Bell System Customer Training Center Manual, 1972-1974; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 2(2/3))
  - New Jersey Bell System Customer Traning Center Manual, 1972-1974; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 3(3/3))
  - New Jersey Bell Customer Training Center Manual, 1974 November 18; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 4(1/3))
  - New Jersey Bell System Customer Training Center Manual, 1974 November 18; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 5(2/3))
  - New Jersey Bell System Customer Training Center Manual, 1974 November 18; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 6(3/3))
  - Northern Telecom Training Center Binder, 1979; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Northeast Electronic Products Catalog Binder, 1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Operational Quality Specification, 1980 April 22; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Packet Switching, 1979; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Paging, 1971-1972, 1975; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - PAS Cables-Port Adaptor System, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - PAS-Port Adaptor System, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - PBX-Private Branch Exchange, 1975-1979; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Phone Power, 1972-1978; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - PMS-Problem Management System, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - PMS-Problem Management System, 1981-1984; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 8(1/2))
  - Power Systems Configuration, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Radio-Notes, Articles, Booklets, Reports, Correspondence, 1969-1978; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - RDS-Resource Definition Statements/I and C-Installation and Configuration Data Base, 1980; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - REA-Request for Engineering Action, 1980 April 29; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - RFPs-Request for Proposals, 1969-1979; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - RFT-Radio Frequency Terminal-Anchor Bolt and Templates, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - RVA-Recorded Voice Announcements, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Common Carriers, 1975-1978; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - SBS Binder-Skyline, On the Circuit, Channels, SBS Today, Uplink, 1983-1986; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - SBS Binder-Marketing Update, News Flash, MRC Review, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 2(1/2))
  - SBS Binder-Marketing Update, News Flash, MRC Review, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 3(2/3))
  - SBS Publications Book #1 Binder, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 4(1/2))
  - SBS Publications Book #1 Binder, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 5(2/2))
  - SBS Publications Book II Binder, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 1(1/2))
  - SBS Publications Book II Binder, Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 2(2/2))
  - SBS Publications Book III Binder, Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 3(1/2))
  - SBS Publications Book III Binder, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 4(2/2))
  - SBS Publications Book IV Binder, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 5(1/2))
  - SBS Publications Book IV Binder, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 1(2/2))
  - SBS Site Survey Checklist and Report, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - SBS/Canadian Skyline Extension, 1983-1985; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - SBS Skyline Corporate Call-Thru Service, 1983-1984; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - SBS Skyline Long Distance (MS-Message Service II), 1982-1984; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - SBS Skyline Toll-Free (MS-Message Service II), 1984; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - SBS Skyline WATS(Wide Area Telecommunications Service) (MS-Message Service-I), 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - SCC-Satellite Communications Controller (Final Design Space), 1977, 1980; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - SCC-Satellite Communications Controller, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - SDEC-Satellite Data Exchange Controller, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - SDM/70-Installation and Interconnect Systems Planning Document, 1981 January; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - SDM/70 Binder, 1980; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 10(1/2))
  - SDM/70 Binder, 1980; Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 11(2/2))
  - Seminars and Courses, 1979 July 20; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Service Bulletins, 1981 April 20; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - SS-Shared Services, 1981 March 9; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - SIM-Site Installation Manual, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - SL-1, 1977-1979; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Specialized Common Carriers, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - SOW-Statement of Work, 1980 March 26; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - STF-System Test Facility, 1980; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Switched Virtual Network Service (SVNS/MS IV/Enhanced CSN-B), 1984 April; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - T-Carrier, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Telco Research Corporation-Large Networks Dailogue: Contrasts and Comparisons, 1979 June 26-27; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Telecommunications-Business Communications Review Seminar Reference Manual, 1975 October 28; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Telecommunications-Business Communications Review Seminar Reference Manual, 1977 April 26; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Teleconferencing, 1980-1982; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Telemax User's Guide, 1976-1978; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Telenet-"All About Your Telenet Public Data Network Invoice" Booklet, 1988 August 5; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Telenet-"Education and Training Employee Course Catalog" Booklet, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Telephone Management Systems, 1976-1978; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 1(1/2))
  - Telephone Management Systems, 1976-1978; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 2(2/2))
  - Telephone Services and Equipment, 1966-1978; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Telephone System Studies, 1976, 1979; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Teletype, 1971-1977; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Telex, 1971, 1975, 1978; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Test Equipment, 1980, 1983; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tool Lists, 1980; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Transponder, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - TCS-Transponder Capacity Service, 1981 May 28; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Trunk Make-Busy, 1982; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - TT and C-Tracking Telemetry and Command, 1979-1981; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - TWX Company, 1970-1979; Series 4 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Voice Communications Handbook-SBS Message Ser, 1982; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 1(1/3))
  - Voice Communications Handbook-SBS Message Services Binder, 1982; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 2(2/3))
  - Voice Communications Handbook-SBS Message Services Binder, 1982; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 3(3/3))
  - Voice Communications, 1974-1978; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 4(1/2))
  - Voice Communications, 1974-1978; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 5(2/2))
  - VPA-Voice Port Adaptor Plug Ins, 1980, 1982; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Voice Quality, 1981 December; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - WATS-Wide Area Telecommunications Service, 1970-1976; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 1(1/2))
  - WATS-Wide Area Telecommunications Service, 1970-1976; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 2(2/2))
  - WATS Studies-Wide Area Telecommunications Service, 1977; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)